http://www.ameriprise.com/legal/website-rules

For Ameriprise Financial internet world wide web sites
Ameriprise Financial, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates ("Ameriprise Financial") requires that all visitors to any of our websites (collectively, the "Site") adhere to the following rules and regulations. By accessing the Site you indicate your acknowledgment and acceptance of these terms and conditions.
The Site is designed for residents of the United States only, and should not be considered a solicitation to buy or an offer to sell any securities or other financial products and services in any other jurisdiction.
Laws and regulations
User access to and use of the Site are subject to all applicable federal, state and local laws and regulations.
Copyright
All information, content, forms, photographs, graphics, and software available on or through the Site (collectively "Content") is owned or controlled by Ameriprise Financial, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates, and other parties. The Content is protected by U.S. and foreign copyright common law rights and statutes. Users are prohibited from modifying, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, publishing, selling, licensing, creating derivative works, or using any Content available on or through the Site for commercial or public purposes, without the prior written permission of Ameriprise Financial, Inc.
Trademarks
The trademarks, service marks, slogans, logos, trade dress and other identifiers ("Marks") displayed on the Site are the property of Ameriprise Financial, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates, and of other parties. The Marks are protected by U.S. and foreign trademark, common law rights and statutes. Users of the Site are prohibited from using any Marks for any purpose including, but not limited to, use on other materials, in presentations, as domain names, or as metatags, without the written permission of Ameriprise Financial, Inc. or such third party that may own the Marks.
All inquiries regarding trademarks and registered marks should be directed to intellectual.property.legal.mail@ampf.com.
The following are some of the most commonly used trademarks and service marks of Ameriprise Financial, Inc., as well as its subsidiaries and affiliates, that may appear on the Site. Other Marks (whether registered or not) that are the property of Ameriprise Financial, Inc., its subsidiaries, affiliates and other parties, also exist throughout the website.
Accumulation Protector Benefit®
Active Portfolios® investments
Ameriprise®
Ameriprise Financial
Ameriprise ONE® Financial Account
Benefit Protector®
Confident Retirement®
Dream Book® guide
Dream > Plan > Track >®
MORE WITHIN REACH®
RiverSource®
Advantage®
AdvanceSource®
Hyperlinking
THIS SITE MAY PROVIDE A LINK TO OTHER SITES BY ALLOWING THE USER TO LEAVE THIS SITE TO ACCESS THIRD-PARTY MATERIAL OR BY BRINGING THE THIRD-PARTY MATERIAL INTO THIS SITE VIA "INVERSE" HYPERLINKS AND FRAMING TECHNOLOGY (A "LINKED SITE"). AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL HAS NO DISCRETION TO ALTER, UPDATE, OR CONTROL THE CONTENT ON A LINKED SITE. THE FACT THAT AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL HAS PROVIDED A LINK TO A SITE IS NOT AN ENDORSEMENT, AUTHORIZATION, SPONSORSHIP, OR AFFILIATION WITH RESPECT TO SUCH SITE, ITS OWNERS, OR ITS PROVIDERS. THERE ARE INHERENT RISKS IN RELYING UPON, USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY INFORMATION FOUND ON THE INTERNET, AND AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL URGES YOU TO MAKE SURE YOU UNDERSTAND THESE RISKS BEFORE RELYING UPON, USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY SUCH INFORMATION ON A LINKED SITE.
No warranties
ALL CONTENT, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES ON THE SITE, OR OBTAINED FROM A WEBSITE TO WHICH THE SITE IS LINKED (A "LINKED SITE"), ARE PROVIDED TO YOU "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY OR ACCURACY.
AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL DOES NOT ENDORSE AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR (A) THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY OPINION, ADVICE OR STATEMENT MADE THROUGH THE SITE BY ANY PARTY OTHER THAN AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL, (B) ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON LINKED SITES OR (C) THE CAPABILITIES OR RELIABILITY OF ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE.
OTHER THAN AS REQUIRED UNDER APPLICABLE CONSUMER PROTECTION LAW, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE WILL AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL OR ITS DATA- OR CONTENT-PROVIDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY A USER'S RELIANCE ON INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, OR USER'S RELIANCE ON ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF ANY OPINION, ADVICE OR OTHER CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE, OR OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE. PLEASE SEEK THE ADVICE OF PROFESSIONALS, AS APPROPRIATE, REGARDING THE EVALUATION OF ANY SPECIFIC OPINION, ADVICE, PRODUCT, SERVICE, OR OTHER CONTENT.
Limitation of liability for use of the site and linked sites
THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND DESCRIPTIONS OF SERVICES PUBLISHED ON THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, AND AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL AND ITS DATA- AND CONTENT-PROVIDERS SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY LIABILITY FOR SUCH INACCURACIES OR ERRORS. AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL AND ITS DATA- AND CONTENT-PROVIDERS DO NOT WARRANT OR REPRESENT THAT THE CONTENT ON THE SITE IS COMPLETE OR UP-TO-DATE. AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL IS UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO UPDATE ANY CONTENT ON THE SITE. AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL MAY CHANGE THE CONTENT ON THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME.
YOU AGREE THAT NEITHER AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL, NOR ITS DATA- OR CONTENT-PROVIDERS, ITS OR THEIR AFFILIATES OR ANY OF ITS OR THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS WILL BE LIABLE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, FOR ANY PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST PROFITS, COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE SERVICE OR LOST OPPORTUNITY) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, OR WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, EVEN IF AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL IS MADE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. FURTHERMORE, YOU AGREE THAT NEITHER AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL NOR ITS DATA OR CONTENT PROVIDERS, OR ITS OR THEIR AFFILIATES OR ANY OF ITS OR THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS WILL BE LIABLE UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY FOR THE TRANSMISSION OF ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT A USER'S EQUIPMENT, FAILURE OF MECHANICAL OR ELECTRONIC EQUIPMENT OR COMMUNICATION LINES, TELEPHONE OR OTHER INTERCONNECT PROBLEMS (E.G., YOU CANNOT ACCESS YOUR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER), UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, THEFT, OPERATOR ERRORS, STRIKES OR OTHER LABOR PROBLEMS OR ANY FORCE MAJEURE. AMERIPRISE FINANCIAL CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THE WEB SITE.
Confidentiality of user communications
Except as required by law and in accordance with the Ameriprise Financial Internet Privacy Statement, [view Ameriprise Financial Internet Privacy Statement]. Ameriprise Financial will maintain the confidentiality of all user communications that contain personal user information and that are transmitted directly to Ameriprise Financial. Investment companies (mutual funds) have their own privacy statements that contain requirements and limitations (provisions) that are separate from the provisions of the Ameriprise Financial privacy statement or the Ameriprise Financial internet privacy statement. Copies of a mutual fund's privacy statement(s) can be obtained directly from the mutual fund's sponsor or distributor.
User should be aware that Linked Sites may contain confidentiality provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein. Ameriprise Financial is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
Linked internet sites
Ameriprise Financial prohibits caching, unauthorized hypertext links to the Site and the framing of any Content available through the Site. Ameriprise Financial reserves the right to disable any unauthorized links or frames and specifically disclaims any responsibility for the Content available on any other Internet sites linked to the Site. Access to any other Internet sites linked to the Site is at the user's own risk.
User should be aware that Linked Sites may contain rules and regulations, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, transmission of personal data provisions, and other provisions that differ from the provisions provided on the Site. Ameriprise Financial is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
No investment advice or offers
Nothing in the Site constitutes investment advice, including Ameriprise Financial filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, or recommendations as to the suitability of any specific product or security. Ameriprise Financial provides investor relations materials for convenience and information only. In addition, investor relations materials and other Web Site Content are not offers to sell or buy or solicitations of an offer to sell or buy any security.
Forward looking information
Certain information on this Site contains certain forward-looking statements, which are subject to risks and uncertainties and speak only to circumstances as of the date on which they are made. The words "believe", "expect", "anticipate", "optimistic", "intend", "aim", "will" or similar expressions are intended to identify forward-looking statements. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only to circumstances as of the date on which they are made. Ameriprise Financial undertakes no obligation to update publicly or revise any forward-looking statements. Important factors that could cause actual results to differ materially from the company's forward-looking statements are described in Ameriprise Financial periodic reports, including the Annual Report on Form 10-K, quarterly reports on Form 10-Q filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission and the Annual Report to Shareholders. Please click here to view such factors contained in the latest Form 10-K from Ameriprise Financial.
Press releases
All press releases and other materials presented or released to the financial community that are contained on the Site were, to the best of the knowledge of Ameriprise Financial, timely and accurate when issued. However, the passage of time can render information stale, and you should not rely on the continued accuracy of any such material beyond the date of issuance. Ameriprise Financial has no responsibility to update any information contained in any such material. All viewers should carefully check the dates of issuance of the material contained in the Site
Transmission of personal data
User acknowledges and agrees that by providing Ameriprise Financial with any personal or proprietary user information through the Site, user consents to the transmission of such personal or proprietary user information over international borders as necessary for processing in accordance with the standard business practices of Ameriprise Financial.
User should be aware that linked sites may contain provisions regarding transmission of personal data that differ from the provisions provided herein. Ameriprise Financial is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
View the Ameriprise Financial Internet Privacy Statement.
Investment companies (mutual funds) have their own privacy statements that contain separate requirements and limitations (provisions) from the provisions of the Ameriprise Financial privacy statement or the Ameriprise Financial internet privacy statement. Copies of a mutual fund's privacy statement(s) can be obtained directly from the mutual fund's sponsor or distributor.
Changes to rules and regulations
Ameriprise Financial reserves the right to revise these Rules and Regulations at any time and users are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any changes to these Rules and Regulations.
Violations of rules and regulations
Ameriprise Financial reserves the right to seek all remedies available at law and in equity for violations of these Rules and Regulations, including the right to block access from a particular Internet address to the Site.
Access to password protected/secure areas
Access to and use of password protected and secure areas of the Site are restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized individuals attempting to access these areas of the Site may be subject to prosecution.
Use of "cookie" file features
Ameriprise Financial reserves the right to store information on a user's computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file for purposes of modifying the Site to reflect users' preferences. The Ameriprise Financial Internet Privacy Statement provides additional information regarding Ameriprise Financial's use of cookies as well as procedures for disabling cookies.
View Ameriprise Financial Internet Privacy Statement, "about Cookies".
Investment companies (mutual funds) have their own privacy statements that contain separate requirements and limitations (provisions) from the provisions of the Ameriprise Financial privacy statement or the Ameriprise Financial internet privacy statement. Copies of a mutual fund's privacy statement(s) can be obtained directly from the mutual fund's sponsor or distributor.
Digital millennium copyright act - notification to Ameriprise Financial regarding alleged copyright infringement
Ameriprise Financial has registered an agent with the United States Copyright Office in accordance with the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the "Act") and avails itself of the protections under the Act. Ameriprise Financial reserves the right to remove any Content on the Site that allegedly infringes another person's copyright. Notices to Ameriprise Financial regarding any alleged copyright infringement on the Site should be directed to Ameriprise Financial General Counsel's Office Attn.: Technology Counsel at intellectual.property.legal.mail@ampf.com.
Jurisdiction/governing law
Users of this Site agree to submit to the laws of the State of Minnesota, USA and applicable federal law without regard to conflicts of laws principles.
